Thank you for watching!
On the first intro...
A leash on the edge of the climax.
Allows you to take a breath between the two chords
Allows you to take a breath between the two chords.
Try to play it.
A leash on the edge of the climax.
Sniphonia
It's very
simple.
......
The thing is that
The groove of the music.
You got it?
I think
a little bit like this.
Oh, the making of the music.
Good morning.
I didn't hear you. I've got my hat on.
Can I ask you to go on?
Yes, ma'am.
Good luck.
Okay, now inside.
Come on in and relax. It's so warm. Here.
It really is. Lucky mall.
Lucky mall.
Sharm Rose.
So pretty.
It's a charmeuse.
It's C.H.R.M.E.
Sharmrose.
People are Sharmroze.
Are you okay?
I was born on June 2nd, so I'm Rose.
I'm Rose.
Bye bye.
Good morning.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Your bangs are shaggy.
Good morning.
It's springtime today. Springtime stage 2023.
Yay.
What's this?
Fruits!
Delicious!
It's chilled.
Let's go!
Yay!
Bye bye!
I made omelette for lunch.
Yay!
I'm going to look for some crepes.
Ta-da!
Oh!
Watch out!
Oh, here it comes!
I'm so happy!
It's so cute! It's so cute!
Look at that! It's so cute!
We got a lot of stuff.
Look at my eyelashes today.
They're amazing!
Balls in a can.
Did you put primer on?
Yeah, it doesn't fall apart.
I brought my own primer and applied it.
Serious eyelash technique.
I said I would do my own eyelashes, and I did.
Bunches.
With two cameras.
It's like there's a filter on them.
It's like I'm not wearing makeup.
I did.
I don't know, it doesn't look like a Taisho outfit.
Julia, when you tied my hair.
I forgot to make her eyes droopy.
I'm going to hold them down.
I'm worried it's going to hurt.
I forgot to do it when I went to Julia's, so I might be pulling my eyes out.
Now, now, now.
Put it back.
Just in case it's really...
This one's up.
It's a little bit like this.
Like this?
I mean, it doesn't match Julia and Julia at all.
There it is.
Oh, my God!
I'm starving.
That was delicious.
Did you take my lunch?
Yeah, I did.
I'm pretty full on dumplings.
Let's try these too.
I took two.
Two?
Okay, fine. I took two, too.
Stop it!
I'm just taking two.
It looks so good.
I just had sesame.
Walnut miso.
If I eat these, my face will get rounder and rounder like a dumpling.
Which one should I have?
The sesame was so good!
I heard this one is good too!
My recommendation!
But I ate this one and took this one too!
I'm so confused!
Miso Noodles looks good too!
I recommend this one
Then I'll have this one
Good morning, I recommend it!
Eh, eh, eh,
Charme Rose.
Sharmrose.
It's not Shal...
It's not Char.
Hello. I spelled it wrong.
The way you read it. I spelled it right.
Everyone thought it was Sharm.
I'm going to eat this and work hard at the hair salon.
I'll do my best.
I ate Hello, too.
Oh, I see.
I've already eaten.
Eat some fruit.
Oh, fruit, too.
Thank you for everything.
Put some in for me. It's always delicious.
Oh, my God.
I feel like I'm going to play the drums a little bit.
Like a Miz King.
Miz King, you know, with the skirts.
Long skirts.
It's really cool!
It's really cool. It's really cool.
I got this one too.
So we have the same set.
I always copy them.
I hate it.
They copy me.
We were just looking at the piano, the opening video and the demon video together.
I checked it out.
It's good.Sounds good.
Oh, yeah! The intermission video, first and last, everyone pay attention!
Well, I've already seen it.
I was looking at it, and I was like, what's that?
Did you feel a sense of "Kishi"?
Did you feel it?
If you're waiting for it, you're right on the money.
That's what I'm aiming for.
If you haven't seen it, you might be wondering what I'm talking about. If you haven't seen it, you might be wondering what I'm talking about.
Well, I don't know if it will go up or not.
If it does, please look at it.
Please do.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Half-twin.
Cute.
I wonder where this one fits in the pin.
Here. Oh, here.
Close.
Half-twin.
Oh, now.
If you put your hairpiece up high...
If you bump it, it will go in the front.
Thank you for your hard work.
Engadina.
Oh no, one hour to go.
I went to see BLACKPINK's concert yesterday, I had a ticket for 2019, but I couldn't go because of my activities, so I was able to go for the first time since then.
Yesterday, I was able to take revenge for that time. I am so happy. It was beautiful, wasn't it?
Yes, it was. Who is your pen?
I can't decide. I can't decide.
No?
I couldn't decide.
I thought Hinata-san and Risa-chan were cute, but I can't decide, so I don't think I will decide yet.
Maybe it's always the same.
I think I'd like to be with any of the groups, but if I knew them, I'd change my mind.
Junior got hooked in 2019, and on the day I got hooked, I got tickets to Tokyo Dome, and I thought for sure I would go, but I couldn't go, so my mom ended up going for me.
That's how it was.
That was the first time.
It was the first time I saw them live.
So it was.
I am so happy.
It was amazing.
This was funny too.
Wet wipes.
It is.
Bunbaiya.
I wonder what it is now.
Only those who came to the concert would know.
But those who didn't find out don't have to be so angry, do they?
It's fine, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Oh, look! Look, look!
Now, let's have a quiz to see what's changed about Hitoka!
In the comments section, please write down what you think I've changed in the next 10 seconds.
The correct answer is
I cut my bangs!
A staff member near me got it right.
Did you all get it?
Yes, that's all.
That's all for Hitoka's quiz corner!
Bye bye!